你能重复一下问题吗
could you repeat the question?
我只听懂了 那个
I only understood the word "the."
可以 尼克松时期的美国
Sure. "In Nixon's America,
你觉得性别平等
"would you say gender equity
不仅仅指的是同工同酬吗
is about more than just equal pay?"
并且问题里并没有 那个 这个词
And the word "the" is not in that question.
好的 下个问题
All right, let's just skip to the next one.
好 到我了
Um, okay, my turn.
随着苏联和东方集体主义的
"As the Soviet Union and the collectivist East
走向极端平等
turn towards radical egalita"--
激等主义 激进平等主义
Tarianism. Radical egalitarianism.
激进平等主义
"Radical egalitarianism,
西方民主国家在其中扮演什么角色
what role do Western democracies have in"--
你知道吗 我觉得你回答不了这个问题
You know what? I don't think you're gonna get this question.
我觉得我们可以做到
I don't see a world where we don't.
废除性别歧视正符合时代潮流
Abolishing gender distinctions is squarely in the zeitgeist.
哪怕有一个记者来采访我们就撞大运了
We'll be lucky if any journalists show up to this,
更别说那些聪明的记者了
let alone the smart ones.
斑比是对的 坚持基本原则
Bambi's right. Stick to the basics.
这个问题基本上都是拉丁语
Hey, this question is mostly in Latin.
-那个  -我知道小猪拉丁
- Mm-hmm. - Oh, I know Pig Latin.
你的性致盎然点是什么
Hey, what are your turn-ons?
还有 你的性致全无点是什么
Oh, and a follow-up, turn-offs.
你想要爱爱的暗示是什么 亲爱的
What's your sign, honey?
我正准备要问呢
Ooh, I was gonna ask that.
第一题的答案是
First question--
我喜欢女孩穿着性感
I like it when girls dress sexy.
真服了
Oh, my God.
我不喜欢她们穿得不性感
I don't like it when they don't.
-错误  -怎么会错呢
- Wrong. - How could it be wrong?
个人意见不同 这点我支持你 兄弟
It's an opinion. And I'm with you, buddy.
你们说得太快了
You guys talk too fast.
这次会议就是这样的吗
Is this what the conference is gonna be like?
-那是必须的  -不可能
- Yes, definitely. - Not a chance.
肯定会的
Yes, it will.
情色文学
令人性奋的新编年史
那个男人 一个美丽的花瓶
That man, that beautiful jar of nothing
不能代表
cannot represent
我们的首期杂志
the premiere issue of our magazine.
他是封面诶
He's on the cover.
他代表个狗屁
He's representing the fuck out of it.
如果你是封面 再有魅力
No one would be interested if it's just you up there,
也不会有人感兴趣的
charming as you may be.
这是我们唯一
This is our only chance
留下第一印象的机会
to make a first impression.
我们要介绍全新的东西
We are introducing something completely new.
我们必须把事情做好
We have to get this right.
也许你是首脑 但他可是首页啊
You may be the brains, but he's the face,
人们认为首页是摇钱树是有原因的
and there's a reason they call the face "the moneymaker."
就是靠首页挣钱呢
It's what makes the money.
好 我知道
Yes, I get it.
他连最简单的手势都不知道
He doesn't understand rudimentary hand signals.
大猩猩学得都比他快
Gorillas catch on faster.
你只剩几天时间了
You got a couple of days.
尽你所能训练他
Train him up as best you can
还有 态度好点
and, I don't know, maybe lose the 'tude.
态尼玛的度
"Lose the 'tude."
今天早上接到市政厅的电话
Got a call from City Hall this morning.
好好享受你对女议员做的警徽恶作剧吧
Enjoy your little badge gag on the councilwoman?
69部队
Troop 69?
艺术部真的太棒了
Yeah, Art Department knocked it out of the park.
现在我们要接受县税评税员的审计了
Well, now we're being audited by the county tax assessor.
你就是忍不住 是吧
Couldn't leave it alone, could you?
韦斯特伯里真该给我个奖章
You know, Westbury should really give me a badge.
奖励我教会我们聪明年轻的一代
Teaching our bright young minds
吃饼干可不止一种方式
that there's more than one way to eat a cookie.
-道格  -你有没有听说
- Doug. - Hey, did you hear
斯科特在整条街发出了通知
Scotty gave notice down the block?
我觉得我们可以在他们雇经纪人之前
I bet we could swoop in, make an offer,
趁火打劫 出价买下那栋楼
and nab that building before they even hire a broker.
-我们没有现金  -我们会有的
- We don't have the cash. - We will.
我们已经在赔钱了
We are bleeding money.
要想挣钱 先要花钱
You gotta spend money to make money.
想要花钱你得先有钱啊
You gotta have money to spend money.
谁说的
Says who?
不用担心审计 我们的账面没问题
Don't worry about the audit. Our books are good.
杰瑞会处理的
Gerry will handle it.
把毛衣脱了 把这个披肩上
Hey, lose the sweater. Throw this over your shoulder.
Annal 编年史 Anal 肛交 谐音梗
情色文学令人性奋的新编年史
- "An exciting new chapter in the annals of erotica."
编年史 是汤普金斯最喜欢的情色作品
Annal is Tompkins favorite kind of erotica.
谁说女权主义不能性感
"Who says feminism can't be sexy? "
捡到宝了
This is gold.
我们得派人去报道这次新闻发布会
We gotta send someone to cover this press conference.
"女性凝视"只是
Is "female gaze" just another way
女同性恋的另一种说法吗
of saying carpet munchers?
看吧 这宝藏开始放光了
See? This stuff writes itself.
有没有人要接这轻松的一单
Anyone up for a fish-in-a-barrel gig?
600字的
600 words.
我接了
I'll take this one.
格伦
Glenn.
格伦x4
all: Glenn, Glenn, Glenn, Glenn,
格伦x6
Glenn, Glenn, Glenn, Glenn, Glenn, Glenn.
维多利亚·哈特尼特
《饱受折磨的妇女参政权论者》
好 我们来复习一下
Okay. Let's review.
女权主义是
Feminism is?
-好事  -还有呢
Good. And?
从女巫那事儿开始的
Started with witches.
不是 怪我
No. that one's on me.
我就不该以塞勒姆女巫审判开场
I should not have opened with the Salem witch trials.
好 我们回过头来说是谁的斗争啊
Okay, let's get back on course in the struggle for.
伊丽莎白·科迪·斯坦顿
Elizabeth Cady Stanton.
这只是我在介绍中
- Was one of the names
提到的名字的其中之一
that I mentioned in the introduction.
-我妈差点就给我取名科迪  -是吗
- My mom almost named me Cody. - Oh.
因为我们的姓他就没有取
But she didn't cause our last name.
她说如果我叫科迪·布洛迪
She said that people wouldn't take me seriously
人们不会把我当回事
if my name was Cody Brody.
她很聪明啊
Well, she sounds like a smart woman.
-你会称她为女权主义者吗  -不会当面叫
Would you call her a feminist? - Not to her face.
干嘛啊 这又不是一个贬义词
Come on. It's not a bad word.
女权主义是关于平等的
Feminism is about equality.
是关乎给予人们力量和话语权
It's about giving people power and a voice,
即便他们只是徒有其表
even if they are some pretty little thing
还不会使用自身力量 为自己发声
that hasn't been taught to use theirs yet.
好了 对不起
Okay. Sorry. Jeez.
现在我明白为什么女性有这么多的参政论者
Now I understand why women have so much suffrage.
好吧
- All right, um...
-咱喝一杯吧  -好啊
how about we have a drink? - Sure.
-好  -有啤酒吗
Okay. - Got any beer?
没有 只有一瓶美味的普依富塞白葡萄洒
No, I do not. I have a lovely Pouilly-Fuisse.
信我 确实美味
Trust me.
你不是要去打保龄球了吗
Shouldn't you be bowling?
我是要去
I should.
我只是来看一眼杰瑞的
I'm taking a look at Gerry's...
说不清是什么 成品
I'm not sure what to call this. Work?
现在 对杰瑞别那么严格 他是一个真正的会计
Now, go easy on Gerry. He's a real accountant.
我好不容易从国会大厦把他挖过来
I poached him from Capitol.
就是他弄清楚
He's the one that figured out
如何销毁菲尔·斯佩克特的枪
how to write off Phil Spector's guns.
这账面真是一团糟 我连会计学位都没有都能看出来
This is a mess, and I don't even have an accounting degree.
我还没有高中学历呢
Well, I don't even have a high-school diploma,
即便是荧虫之光
yet here we are.
也敢与日月争辉
To, uh, punching above our weight.
干杯
Cheers.
你的事业确实很成功
You do run a successful business. Sloppily.
-谢谢夸奖  -也糙得很
- Thank you. - Sloppily.
你一半的职员都有犯罪记录
Half your employees have criminal records.
另一半很幸运没有犯罪记录
The other half are lucky they don't.
你把不是你的钱
You're spending money you don't have
花在了你不需要的东西上
on things you don't need.
你太主观了
- Subjective.
别急
Come on. Hold on now.
看看 看看弗兰克发来了什么
Look at what-- look at what Frank sent over.
乳房之塔
The Tower That Titty Built.
别忘了我们的新朋友 老屌蛋
Don't forget our new friend, good old cock and balls.
你难道不想每天
You're telling me you wouldn't want to show up
都来这里工作
to work here every day?
我们的计划 小廷 这个计划
Come on, Tins, our plan. This plan.
发行量大 广告商多 财源广进
Big circulation, big advertisers, big money.
是我们当年一起
The same plan that we came up with
坐在雪佛兰英帕拉里制定的计划
in the back of that'64 Impala,
彻夜吹牛
talking out of our asses,
历历在目 熠熠生辉
is as alive now as it has ever been.
是吗
Yeah?
是啊
Yeah.
你已经着手准备了
You're on top of it?
跟饿虎扑食似的
Like a duck on a June bug.
那你应该知道账面上少了5万
Then you must know 50 grand is missing from these books.
-我不知道  -是吗
- No, I didn't. - Hmm.
你不知道
You didn't know that.
现在我知道了
Well, now I do.
因此 父权制迫使男性
So the patri-archie forces men
扮演他们也不想扮演的角色
into roles they don't want to play either.
好家伙 我想他知道了
By George, I think he's got it.
我叫是谢恩 不是好家伙
It's Shane.
好吧
Yeah.
你是一个好老师
- But you're a good teacher.
谢谢
Thank you.
我碰见的大部分女孩
Most of the girls--
女人 对我谈论的东西
women I meet aren't interested
都不感兴趣
in what I have to talk about.
能看得出来你很敏感
Well, I can tell that you're a very sensitive man.
我知道消防员应该很强硬
I mean, I know firemen are supposed to be tough,
我也不怕火什么的
and, like, I'm not afraid of fire or anything.
你应该怕火
Probably should be.
但有时候其他人
But sometimes the other guys,
他们都很刻薄
they can just be so...mean.
比如说有一次 我从着火的大楼里
Like, one time, I rescued this cat
救了一只猫
from a burning building.
我冲出去以后发现它没有了呼吸
I rushed outside, but it wasn't breathing.
我就对它做人工呼吸 这对动物也管用
So I gave it mouth-to-mouth, which totally works on animals.
要我就不会想到人工呼吸
I would never have thought to do that.
但是当天晚上在浴室里
But that night in the showers,
其他人一直对我学猫叫 喵 喵
the other guys, they just kept meowing and meowing.
我跑到9号消防车藏了起来
- I ran and hid in engine number nine.
那些男人 他们并不强硬
Those men, they're not tough.
他们只是害怕 害怕变得脆弱
They're just scared, scared of being vulnerable.
现在 我可以对你说 如果女人成为了消防员
Now, I can tell you that if women were firefighters,
没有人会因为
then no one would ridicule you
你救了一只无助的小猫咪嘲笑你
for saving a helpless little kitty cat.
真可惜女人不能当消防员
Too bad women can't be firemen.
谁说的
Says who?
那个 名字里就写着呢
Well, it's right there in the name.
-火男 消防员  -好吧
Fireman. - Okay.
而且 你还要能够负重190磅
Oh, but also, you have to be able to carry 190 pounds.
是吗 很重吗
Oh, really? Is that a lot?
我就有190磅
You're looking at a buck-90.
好吧 我试试
Well, okay. May I?
我的天 不
Oh, my God. No.
坚持住
Hold on.
我想如果我
I'm sure if I just, you know--
受过适当的训练什么的
I had the proper training and everything,
就会
then, you know...
我能说你很好看吗
Am I allowed to say you're pretty?
我并不会因为你夸我漂亮而指责你物化我
Well, I wouldn't accuse you of objectifying me if you did.
让我
Let me just--
-舞动 舞动起来  -我的天啊
♪ Sookie, sookie now ♪ - Oh, my God.
真着火的话 我会扛着你逃出大楼
Now, in a real fire, I'd be carrying you
而不是去卧室
out of the building and not into the bedroom.
幸运的是 现场唯一的火源就是我们的欲火
Lucky for us, the only thing on fire is our libidos.
不 没有火源
No, no, no. It's okay.
这只是一个高级词用来描述
It's just a fancy way of saying that you're--
描述我很感性趣
that I--I am--I am very excited about this.
我口中的甜美
♪ A sweet taste in my mouth ♪
这跟我平常
Um, and this is not something I ever normally...
做得不一样
Wow. Do.
我的天
Oh, my God.
快乐幸福
♪ Happily, nah-nah ♪
在一所大房子里
♪ In a great big ol'roomy house ♪
我知道你要
♪ And I know you're gonna ♪
将我占有 宝贝
♪ Groove me, baby ♪
但是 我想 为什么不呢
- But, you know, I guess. why not?
我感觉良好
♪ Make me feel good inside ♪
来吧 和我共舞 宝贝
♪ Come on, and groove me, baby ♪
我要你让我心动
♪ I need you to groove me ♪
好了 好了 亲爱的
♪ Oh, yeah, now, now, darling ♪
来吧 来吧
♪ Uh, come on, come on ♪
嘿 亲爱的
♪ Hey, there, sugar darlin' ♪
来吧 给我点什么
♪ Come on, give me something ♪
妹子
♪ Girl... ♪
我只是想让你爽
I just want to make you feel good.
真的吗
You do?
是的 我很好 很爱你
♪ Yes, I'm good, good loving ♪
很多很多的拥抱
♪ With plenty, plenty hugging ♪
好的
Okay.
你让我感觉很爽
♪ You make me feel good inside ♪
来吧 和我共舞 宝贝
♪ Come on, and groove me, baby ♪
爱抚我 宝贝
♪ Move me, baby ♪
离我更近一点 美女
♪ Oh, sock it to me, mama ♪
喂
Hello?
-嘿 亲爱的  -喂
- Hey, honey. - Hello.
就是打电话来提醒你
- Just calling to remind you
今天要编辑照片
about the editor's photo today.
你把衣服挑好了吗
You have the clothes picked out?
当然
- I surely do.
今天早上某人很开心啊
Ooh, someone's chirpy this a.m.
某人昨晚过得很开心
Someone had a very fun night.
-噢 某人是不是  -是的
- Oh, my--did someone have-- - Yes! Yes.
甚至不局限于忠诚的伴侣关系
And not even in the confines of a committed partnership.
我有一夜情了
I had a one-night stand.
-不是吧  -真的
- No! - Yes.
把这条从你的单子上划掉吧
Well, check that off your list.
你怎么知道我有个单子的
How do you know about my list?
像你这样的女孩总是有个单子
Girls like you always have a list.
体验非常超越
Oh. Well, it was transcendent.
我不知道自己怎么了
I don't know what came over me.
然后 然后 他好像看透了我的心思
And then--and then, like he read my mind,
就这么走了
he was just gone.
猜猜谁带了扭蕉包
Guess who brought croy-sants.
这是法语 意思是牛角包
It's French for pastry.
我得挂了
I have to go.
屌钟为你而鸣
The bell tolls for thee.
你跟所有人都说了
You told everyone?
这里看起来像是要谨慎的地方吗
Does this look like a place of discretion?
哎呀 不要贬低这种事
- Oh, come on. Don't cheapen it.
因为我已经贬低过了
'Cause I already did!
谁是那个幸运的家伙啊
So who's the lucky guy?
-淑女从不  -老实交代
- A lady never-- - Uh-uh, spill.
所有细节都要说
Yeah, we want details.
好吧 是谢恩
Wait, it was Shane.
-不是吧  -还有
- No. - Yes.
-你们昨晚有练习  -就这么发生了
You had training last night. - It just happened.
你知道的 就几次
You know, a few verres de vin.
-就结束了  -看看你
- I so called it. - Mm, look at you.
利用你在出版业的强势地位
Using your powerful position in publishing
给自己整点零食
to score some tail.
哦 宝贝
Ooh, baby.
某些人在玩火呢
Someone's playing with fire.
是你们让我这么做的
You all told me to do it!
那是在我们雇他之前 乔伊斯
Before we hired him, Joyce.
这很不专业
So unprofessional.
别听他的 这是你应得的
Don't listen to him. You deserve it.
我现在的五个跟踪者中
Mm, three of my five current stalkers
有三个是前雇主
were former employers.
不 不是那样的
No, it's not like that.
你才是要担心新闻发布会的人
You were the one worried about the press conference,
现在你却让这孩子有了
and now you've gone and given this boy
别的事可想
something else to think about.
这种说法也许符合你的俗艳行为
That narrative may fit your tawdry affairs,
但我可以向你保证
but I can assure you
我的眼睛正盯着你的球呢
that my eye is squarely on the ball.
哪一个 这个还是这个
Which one? This one or this one?
我得回去取证了
I'm gonna have to go back and do some forensics here.
我收到的收据
I mean, the receipts I get
都是在纸片上
are on scraps of paper, matchbooks,
火柴盒上 有时是在卫生纸上
toilet tissue sometimes.
我能让我们整理好真是个奇迹
It's a frigging miracle I get us in the ballpark.
你可以相信我的话 这些数字加起来不合理
You can take my word, those numbers don't add up.
-差得可多了  -这是我的笔迹吗
- And it's a very big ballpark. - Is that my handwriting?
你知道吗 这是我妻子的眼镜
You know what? These are my wife's glasses.
就这样吧 杰瑞
That'll be all, Gerry.
我是说 他不是骗子
I mean, he's not a crook.
-只是个糟糕的会计  -同意
- Just a terrible accountant. - Agreed.
我们为什么不把部队集合起来
Why don't we round up the troops?
肯定有人知道些什么
Somebody's gotta know something.
你最好坦白 因为我们已经知道了
You might as well come clean because we already know.
关于我们销赃的那台复印机吗
About the copy machine we fenced?
当然 我把相机当掉了 但我买了更好的
Sure, I pawned the cameras, but I bought better ones,
而且我还交了房租 真是双赢
and I also made rent, so win-win.
妹子 外面的世界很大很大
♪ Girl, there's a big, big world out there ♪
在1970年秋天到1971年春天之间
Between the fall of 1970 and the spring of 1971,
严格来说 我确实住在这里
yeah, technically, I did live here.
但那只是因为我躲起来了
But that's just 'cause I was hiding
躲我犯的罪过
from the Lambs of God.
哦 那些是我的
Oh, those are mine.
新车
New Pinto.
用一个自然死亡的
Bought with money from a dead aunt
姑妈的钱买的
who died of natural causes.
-她杀了她姑妈吗  -是的
- Did she kill her aunt? - Yes.
这就是你周三凌晨两点喝醉了雇人
This is what happens when you hire people
就因为人家在飞镖比赛中打败了你的后果
2: 00 a. m. drunk on a Wednesday because they beat you at darts.
肯尼是我们最好的文案编辑
Kenny was the best copy editor we've ever had.
我到死都要为他辩护
I'|I defend that hire till the day I die.
真正的企业不是这样运作的
Real businesses don't operate this way.
好 那你想让我怎么做
All right. So what do you want me to do?
把大家都炒了 清理门户是吗
Fire everyone? Just clean house?
不 但我们从某个地方开始
No, but we gotta start somewhere.
好
Fine.
我们炒掉杰瑞
We'll fire Gerry.
-我很高兴  -谢谢
I'm glad we're doing this. - Thank you.
我也是
Me too.
明天是大日子了
Um, tomorrow is the big day,
我只是想确认一下
and I just wanted to make sure
我们都明白现在是什么情况
that we're both understanding what this is.
-看起来像炸鱿鱼  -是的 是的
- Looks like fried squid to me. - Yes. Yeah.
这是我们点的菜
That is the food that we ordered.
但在更深层次上
But on a deeper level...
我们的关系中存在着权力不均
there are power dynamics in our relationship.
我就喜欢你说些聪明词儿
I love when you say smart things.
这种情况使得自愿的问题变得复杂
And, uh, those dynamics make issues of consent complicated.
-等等 我有麻烦了吗  -不 不 完全不是
- Wait, am I in trouble? - No, no, no, not at all.
只是
It's just, um...
昨晚很开心
last night was fun.
很开心
Very fun.
但是也只是娱乐而已
But it was just fun.
我明白你的意思
Yes. I understand what you're saying.
只是娱乐而已
It was just fun.
嗯 对 很好
- Right. Yes. Oh, God, good.
好吧 因为我们是同事
Okay. Cause we're working together.
没人说你不能在一起工作的时候找点乐子
No one says you can't have some fun
但我们都知道这是什么
while you're working together, but we both know what this is.
我很高兴你说了出来
I am so glad you said something,
因为我也在想
because it was on my mind too.
我甚至都不去这些厕所
I don't even use these to go to the bathroom.
你要去哪里
Where do you go?
什么 不 我要用洗手间
What? No, I use bathrooms.
我只是不去公共场合 天啊 继续
I just don't go in public. Oh, my God, just keep--
袋底钱
发布会
我应该推出更高档的标志
I should have debuted the classier logo.
你好 诺曼
Hello, Norman.
底袋钱十年来出了20刊
20 Bottom Dollar titles in a decade,
而只有这部能吃上一顿大餐的
and this is the one that gets a fancy lunch.
看看你
Look at you.
威廉·伦道夫·赫斯特重生
William Randolph Hearst reborn.
你知道这里面全是鸡巴和
You know this one's full of dongs
女人的意见 对吧
and lady opinions, right?
《山谷色情信使》包罗万象
"The Valley Porn Courier" covers all things
袋底钱 不只是我觉得有吸引力
Bottom Dollar, not just what I find appealing.
这是我对读者许下的承诺
That's a promise I made to my readers.
-诺曼  -你的头号粉丝
- Norman. - Your number-one fan.
我带您去贵宾席
Let me show you to your VIP seat.
-当然  -我们知道他会出现
- Of course. - We knew he would show up.
-其他人呢  -是啊 没料到
What about everyone else? - Yeah, it's a-- it's a turnout.
-瞧  -我喜欢
- Voila. - I like it.
-真的吗  -嗯
- You do? - I do.
我们外面挤得水泄不通
- We are packed to the gills out there.
你又跟他上床了
Ah, you screwed him again.
粗鲁不得体
Boorish and inappropriate.
但是准确
And accurate.
没事的 一切尽在掌控之中
It's fine. It's fine. It's under control.
好
Good.
-你还好吗  -嗯 没事
You okay? - Yeah. I'm fine.
只是 这里真的有人耶
It's just, um, there's actually people here.
是啊 因为我们的杂志是新事物冲击波
Yeah, because our magazine is a jolt of something new.
是耳语和尖叫
It's a whisper and a scream.
我想是的 别搞砸了 好吗
I guess it is. Just, uh, don't blow it, okay?
-好的  -别理他
Okay. - Just ignore him.
我支持你的性探索
I support your sexploits.
你早该这么做了
You should've been doing this a lot sooner.
我知道
- I know. - Mm-hmm.
他为什么那么心烦意乱
God. What was he so hung up about?
想想看 那些自由的爱情
Just think, all of that free love
就在那里等着你拿 不知怎么的
out there for the taking, and somehow,
我还以为我得付钱呢
I thought I would have to pay for it.
抱歉我迟到了
Sorry I'm late.
爸爸的货车抛锚了
Pop's van broke down.
-现在是这样了是吗  -你带你爸爸来了
- Oh, we're doing that. - You brought your dad?
我父母都来了 他们超级为我骄傲
Both my parents. They're super proud of me.
我是家里第一个
I'm the first person in my family
出席新闻发布会的人
to attend a press conference.
嘿 时间到了
Hey, it's time.
别紧张 我们做足了准备
Don't be nervous. We did the work.
-你会表现得很好的  -我不紧张
You're gonna do great. - I'm not nervous.
这也许是有史以来第一次 我清楚地知道自己想要什么
For the first time, maybe ever, I know exactly what I want.
很好 利用这一点
Well, great. Use that.
-是你  -什么
- It's you. - What?
你是史上最性感的老师
You're, like, the sexiest teacher ever,
除了还没结婚 还有 我现在到年纪了
except not married, and, also, I'm of age now.
不是 好吧 不 等一等 我们只是在娱乐
No. Okay. No, hold on. We were just having fun.
是的 就是这样开始的 一颗火花
Yeah, that's how it started-- with a spark.
但没有火花的爱还算什么
But what's love without a spark?
《风骚女子》是
Uh, "Minx" is a--
《风骚女子》会建立起
Oh, "Minx" will establish
女性凝视
the female gaze, uh...
我们正处在女权主义和色情文学
We are at the exciting intersection
激动人心的交汇处
of feminism and erotica.
有什么问题吗
Any questions?
好吧
Okay, uh
我想介绍一下谢恩·布罗迪
I would like to introduce Shane Brody.
谢恩从无数申请者中脱颖而出
Shane was selected out of countless applicants
因为他是最符合我们风格的
because he was the minxiest.
他是一个现代男性
He is a modern man.
他很支持我们的使命
He's a supporter of our mission,
而且他也是
and he's also--
经认证的A级男人肉体
A certified piece of Grade-A man-meat.
您说是就是
Ank-you-thay.
谢恩 告诉我们你到底做了什么
Yeah, for Shane, tell us what you really had to do
才得到的这份工作
to get the job.
我给老板留下好印象吧
I guess impress the boss.
你妈妈看过你的初次登刊吗
Has your mother seen your debut?
你自己问她 她就在那里
Ask her yourself. She's right there.
-爱您 妈妈  -我也爱你
Love you, Mom. - I love you too.
好孩子
That's my boy.
好的 让我们回到
Okay. Let's just pivot back to the
-你的性趣是什么  -什么让你性致全无
- What are your turn-ons? - Turn-offs?
你想要爱爱的暗示是什么 亲爱的
What's your sign, honey?
告诉我们你理想中的女人
Tell us about your ideal woman.
是啊 你是单身吗 有没有结婚
Yeah, are you single? Is there a Mrs. Man-Meat?
-嗯 我有新女友了  -哦 不
Yeah, I do have a new lady. - Oh, no.
她聪明 优雅 强壮
She's smart, classy, strong.
她可能能举起这里的任何人
She could probably lift anyone in here.
开始了
It's happening.
她很有耐心 举止得体 教人很多东西
She's patient, proper, a teacher,
而且她不需要穿得很性感
and she doesn't have to dress sexy
因为她本来就很性感
'cause she already is.
天啊 谢恩爱上了乔伊斯
- Oh, my God. Shane's in love with Joyce.
她还知道怎么找乐子
- Oh, and she knows how to have just fun,
那种更纯粹的乐趣
which is, like, a more pure kind of fun
毕竟正坠入爱河呢
'cause you're falling in love.
我们在小马托尼的浴室里
Oh, and when we did it in the bathroom
做爱的时候 我发现
at the Tony Pony, I realized--
还没有任何人问的问题
That no one has asked us a single question
是关于这本研究仔细
about this very carefully researched
且考虑周到的杂志呢
and thoughtful magazine.
所以还有人有问题吗
So does anyone have a question?
有的
Yeah.
我是《少年》杂志的格伦·霍林斯沃思
Glenn Hollingsworth, "Lad" magazine.
格伦 你有问题是吧
Glenn, you have a question.
是的
I do.
你想对所有会对《风骚女子》感到好奇
What do you say to all the female readers out there
却又被内容吓着的女性读者
who might be curious about "Minx"
说些什么吗
but are also intimidated by its content?
谢谢你 格伦 这是个好问题
Thank you, Glenn. That's a great question.
这个嘛
Uh, well--
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
-谢谢 乔伊斯  -没事
- Thanks, Joyce. - Yeah.
我欠你个大人情
I owe you something big.
-有点问题可能确实有点尴尬  -是啊
- These can be brutal. - Yeah.
小事情 不必挂齿
A little softball never hurt.
这本杂志看起来很棒
The magazine looks great.
真的 恭喜你
It really does. Congratulations.
非常感谢
Thank you. It means a lot.
也许我们可以找个时间吃午饭
Maybe we can do lunch sometime.
当然好啊
Sure. Why not?
不过不是在俱乐部
But not at the club.
是啊 毕竟你被终身禁入
Yeah, no, you're banned for life.
他们把你的照片放在前面
They put your picture up front.
真的吗 那个人是谁来着
They did? Like--who's that guy?
那个在网球比赛上裸奔的人
That guy that streaked the tennis tournament?
-斯图  -斯图 对啊
- Stu. - Stu. Stu, yeah.
-嗨  -天哪
Hey. - Oh, God.
你想偷走我的女孩吗
You trying to steal my girl?
是女人
Woman.
自由女性不会被偷走
Liberated woman who cannot be stolen
她们不是物品
and is not property.
说得对
That's right.
回头我打给你
Well, um, I'll call you.
-好吗  -嗯
Okay? - Mm-hmm.
我们要去玛丽·卡兰德家
We're going to Marie Callender's.
我们吗
We?
他们想见你
They want to meet you.
想像我一样了解你 除了做爱那部分
Get to know you like I do, but not have sex.
好吧 停下
Okay. No, stop.
我想我们得
All right, I think we need to--
我们之间有点误会
There's been a misunderstanding here, okay?
这不是真的 我们不是情侣
Cause this isn't real. We're not a couple.
我去见你那热情的父母
It's not appropriate for me
还不太合适 好吗
to meet your very enthusiastic parents, okay?
我们只是普通的性关系
It was just sex. It was just casual sex.
只是"找乐子"罢了
That's what "just fun" means.
所以你利用了我
So you used me.
我们在互相利用
We were using each other,
是正向利用 为了愉悦
in a good way, for pleasure.
别给我的行为下定义
Don't tell me what I was doing.
你说每个人都该为自己发声 对吗
You say everyone deserves their own voice, right?
还是我对你来说只是一个可爱的小物件
Or am I just some pretty little thing to you?
好吧 我知道你什么意思了
Okay. All right. Okay. I see what you're doing.
不是的 因为你只是个
But that--no, that's not this, because you're just someone
在我手底下工作
who technically works for me
然后和我做了爱的人
who I then had sex with.
-我信任过你  -谢恩
- I trusted you. - Shane.
我让你用过我的阴茎 现在我要收回
I gave you my penis, and I want it back.
我不想再出现在你的杂志上了
I don't want to be in your magazine anymore.
编辑女士
Madam editor.
刚开始还不太出色 之后就一鸣惊人
It was a little shaky at first, and then boom.
省省吧 谢恩退出了
Save it. Shane's pulled out.
我伤了他的心
I broke his simple little heart.
我很遗憾 但他签了合同
Well, I'm sorry, but he signed the contract,
也就是说我们拥有这些照片 我们要发表
which means we own the photos, so we're publishing them,
所以他没法阻止我们
and there's nothing that he can do about it.
不过 我之前怎么说的
Though, what did I say?
天哪 你喜欢代价惨重的胜利
Oh, God, you love a Pyrrhic victory.
我不知道那是什么意思 所以伤不到我
I don't know what that means, so it doesn't hurt my feelings.
道格 我们不能未经允许
Doug, we cannot publish naked photos of Shane
就发布谢恩的裸照
without his permission.
虽然说从法律角度来说是可以
I mean, yeah, fine, we're legally allowed to,
但那算传达了什么信息呢
but what kind of message does that send?
会传达出我们生意不错的信息
It would send the message that we're good at business.
这可不是第一次
Look, this is hardly the first time
模特临阵退缩了
a model has gotten cold feet.
是啊 但我们得做得更好
Yeah, but we have to be better than that.
必须 其实我坚持
We have to. In fact, I insist
我们要达到更高的标准
on holding us to a higher standard.
听听你说的 "更高的标准"
Listen to you. "A higher standard."
就因为你不能管好你的阴道
Because you couldn't keep your vag in your pants.
你非要这么粗鲁吗
Do you always have to be so crass?
好吧 乔伊斯 我摊牌了
All right, Joyce, I'm gonna give it to you straight.
杂志已经印刷了
The magazine is printed.
我在这本破杂志上花的钱
And I spent more on this rag
比我做过的任何事都多
than anything that I have ever done.
我在最后一刻不顾大家的建议
I upped our print run to 500, 000
把印刷量增加到了50万份
at the last minute against the advice of everyone.
如果我把这个问题扯进来
If I were to pull this issue,
我们就完了
we'd be done.
我就会跌进
And I would be in a hole
巨大的深渊
so goddamn deep
很多年后才能爬出来了
that it would take me years to climb out of.
所以
So...
要么接受 要么解决
get okay with this or fix it.
杰瑞接班人的简历
Resumes for Gerry's replacement.
我以为我们只在周五解雇员工
I thought we only fired people on Fridays.
你又没解雇过人
You've never fired anyone.
好吧
All right.
简直疯了
This is insane.
我能和你谈谈吗
Can I talk to you?
我拿了钱
I took the money.
不过你已经知道了
But you already knew that.
不停换一大堆不规律的标题
A bunch of transfers between off-cycle titles
还同时从打印机发出意外发票
at the same time as a surprise invoice from the printer?
-这招只能糊弄杰瑞  -我就知道你不会同意的
- That shit may fool Gerry-- - I knew you wouldn't approve.
你的宠物计划让我们亏空
Your pet project is bleeding us dry,
现在你偷自己的东西还瞒着我
and now you're stealing from yourself to hide it from me?
好吧 也许我只是不想让你
Okay, maybe I just didn't want you looking at me
用现在这样的眼神看我
the way you are looking at me right now.
我改变主意了 廷娜
I changed the plan, Tina.
-对不起  -开始了
I am sorry. - That's a start.
我们都知道你对这个地方意味着什么
We both know what you mean to this place.
你是袋底钱的另一半
You are the other half of Bottom Dollar.
我只是需要你在这件事上相信我
I just-- I need you to trust me on this one.
虽然我超爱你的商业头脑
Push down those business smarts
但我现在要你把那些抛之脑后 相信我
that I fucking love about you and trust me.
你知道眼睁睁地
You know how hard it is
看着起火了却不去救火有多难吗
to see a burning building and not yell fire?
可能还没到起火的地步呢
Well, maybe it's not on fire.
可能只是温度高 不太舒服
Maybe it's just hot and uncomfortable.
这就是你思考的地方吗
Is this where you come to think?
不 我在这工作
No, this is my job.
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
我想和你谈谈
I wanted to talk to you.
最好快点
Better make it fast,
因为如果发生火灾 我就得走了
'cause if there's a fire, I'm gonna have to go.
我觉得《风骚女子》
I think "Minx" is
对你来说是一个巨大的机会
a tremendous opportunity for you.
我知道我们没怎么谈过
And I know that we haven't talked much
你的希望和梦想
about your hopes and dreams,
但当模特可以帮你打开路子
but modeling can open a lot of doors.
更多模特生意
More modeling.
表演
Acting.
你可以成为明星
You could be a star.
我不想成为明星
I don't want to be a star.
我想要400美元 向世界展示我的老二
I wanted 400 bucks and to show my dick to the world.
好吧 我本不想走到这个地步
AI right, well, I was hoping it wouldn't come to this,
但你签了合同
but you signed a contract,
袋底钱有你照片的所有权
and Bottom Dollar owns your photos,
所以我们两个都无能为力
so there's nothing either one of us can do about it.
你说了这么多女权的东西
So after all that feminist stuff,
就归结为一张纸吗
it just comes down to a piece of paper?
是的 谢恩
Yes, Shane.
这是公事
This is business.
我来这只是为了公事
And I am here on business and business only.
天呐 你是我睡过的第四个男人
God, you're the fourth guy that I have ever slept with
唯一不是我男朋友的一个
and the only one who wasn't my boyfriend
但活最好
and by far the best,
虽然更多是因为我的身体
but that has more to do with my relationship
但我还是觉得
to my own body, I think, but still, it was, um, uh.
你比我喜欢你
You were more into me
还要喜欢我 我知道
than I was into you, and I knew that.
我应该更谨慎一点的
I should have been more careful.
我只是想找回感觉
I just wanted to feel good again,
所以我推卸了所有责任
so I pushed away all reason,
这样确实太自私了
and that was really selfish.
太不负责任了
It's so irresponsible.
你本可以跟我父母打个招呼的
You could have said hi to my parents.
是啊 我该打招呼的
Yes, I should have.
如果你不想上《风骚女子》
If you don't want to be in "Minx,"
不论后果如何 我都会想办法
then I will figure out a way of killing the issue,
解决这个问题
no matter the consequences.
你有发声的权利
You deserve to have a voice.
我不在乎他们的话
♪ I don't care what they say ♪
干得不错
Nice work.
你还尝到了点额外甜头
And you got some in the process.
需要帮忙可以找我
Let me know if you need help.
谢谢你 蒂娜
Thank you, Tina.
你看不出我为你的触碰而活吗
♪ Can't you see I live for your touch? ♪
因为我相信你
♪ Because I believe in you ♪
我还能说什么
♪ What else can I say? ♪
我相信你 女孩
♪ I believe in you, girl ♪
如果我在努力 那就走吧
♪ If I'm trying to be, go on your way ♪
-22英寸  -斑鳟鱼
- 22 inches. - Brown trout?
-彩虹  -闭嘴
- Rainbow. - Shut up.
这不是八月封面先生吗
Well, if it isn't Mr. August.
更像是八月封面太太
More like Mrs. August.
他的老二真花哨
His dick's so fancy,
可能都湿不了了
it probably can't even get wet anymore.
你们就笑吧
You guys can all laugh,
我替你们感到难过
but I'm the one that feels bad for you.
你们是受害者
You're victims,
斧拳（父权）的受害者
victims of something called the patri-archie.
总有一天 你们会懂的
Someday, you'll understand.
你和我
♪ You and I ♪
随着不同鼓点的节奏旅行
♪ Travel to the beat of a different drum ♪
从我奔跑的样子你看不出来吗
♪ Ah, can't you tell by the way I run ♪
每当你向我抛媚眼
♪ Every time you make eyes at me ♪
喔哦
♪ Whoa ♪
你哭哭啼啼
♪ You cry and moan ♪
说一切都会好的
♪ And say it will work out ♪
但亲爱的孩子 我心存疑虑
♪ But, honey child, I've got my doubts ♪
只见树木 不见森林
♪ You can't see the forest for the trees ♪
不要误解我
♪ So don't get me wrong ♪
这并非我本意
♪ It's not that I knock it ♪
只是我
♪ It's just that I ♪
不在市场上
♪ I'm not in the market ♪
等待一个只爱我的男孩
♪ For a boy who wants to love ♪
只爱我
♪ Only me ♪
没错 我不是说
♪ Yes, and I ain't saying ♪
你不漂亮
♪ You ain't pretty ♪
我只是想说我还没准备好
♪ All I'm saying's I'm not ready ♪
迎接试图控制我的
♪ For any person, place, or thing ♪
任何人 任何地点 任何事
♪ To try and pull the reins ♪
控制我
♪ In on me ♪
所以再见了
♪ So goodbye ♪
我要走了
♪ I'll be leaving ♪
我觉得哭哭啼啼
♪ I see no sense ♪
毫无意义
♪ In this crying and grieving ♪
如果你的生活没有我
♪ We'll both live a lot longer ♪
我们会活得更久
♪ If you live without me ♪